[music]
don't lose Your Way When each passing
day youve come so far don't throw it
away
[music]
it gives me great pleasure to address
All Of You last Year I am very happy to see
that we started the employ recognition
Awards and I would really like to than
the organizing commit under anan Who
has done such a great J in terms of
popularizing the emp recognition Award
in terms of making that the nominations
are correctly buil in terms of making
that we a corre kind of people and I
would also like to than the  hires of
vietn across the length and of the count
the to the sou to the central to all
provincial branches Where people have
parp in this sent in their nominations
and have made the emp rec
su and when i look at some of the
examples of the People w the
a happ to see that the respect prin are
Al in Vietnam and as We Grow as We ach
suc We are Building on the right prines
on the right val going for There are
many challenges Vietnam FA but The corre
people and the corre of behav rely on
the prines I sur that face
challenges and  We will even
more than you to stand.
If we hold on to it,
I know our dream will never
die. We will strive for
[music]
[Applause]
the desire to find an
opportunity to work for a
leading financial corporation in Vietnam, a
clear direction for
our employees to get
used to the
[music]
multifaceted nature of it. The plan
will be later, meaning the afternoon of the
[music] month.
10 of the largest employers in Vietnam, and each employer in Vietnam has a history
as far as
this company goes. We have a large number
of employees who work with Vietnam. The
last years, and some even
more, the company and one of the reasons indeed. The
most
important reason why Prudential Vietnam
is so successful is the culture of Prudential
Vietnam. It is because of the Pride and
Passion that each employee has, and I
believe that the respect principle on
which Prudential Vietnam has been
founded, the respect principle which has
governed the way each and every employee
behaves, is one of the key reasons for
the success of Prudential Vietnam. Thank you,
sir.
Thank you, sir. What is this?  Received from you for the
second time after several years, 3 or 4 years, the third
[Applause]
[Music]
is filming
[Applause]
[Music]
like a movie, flying in slowly,
congratulations, leading the way. Every month there's
someone, so proud
[Music]
[Music] [
Music]
call
us for
[Music]
[Applause] [Music]
for
you [Music] the
light, our
heart
[Music]
everyone. If we hold on to
together, I know our dreams will never
die for
[Music]
also in Dad, this is Anan,
the person who has a gift
[Applause]
congratulations, keep trying
[Music]
so beautiful, amazing [Music
]
never [
Music]
attached here, this is it.
Congratulations to
you, company,
congratulations
[Music] [
Music]
[Applause]
how to keep it, where can I get it?
Brother
Ti, the best,
let this be
my own.
[Music]
Let's take The Last one year and the
last vi. A
last year has been an exception, good for us
in the middle of business performance, and this
year on the right, we were the first company to launch. I believe in the of vi. When I heard that Phuong, an employee in the agency management department, was elected the best employee of the year
2007, I was very honored because,
honestly, Phuong is a great person, an
employee working in the
agency management department and loved by many agents
as well as colleagues. The
10 best employees of the company,
those who always embody and promote the
good spirit of respect, making valuable contributions
to the success and sustainable development
of Pruden Show Vietnam,
I would like to invite the four individuals who received the title of
outstanding employee of the
first anniversary Star program. I would like to invite
Ms. Hoang
[Music],
Mr. Nguyen Tri Dung from the department from Quy Nhon city,
Mr. H Thanh from Hai Phong city,
Mr. H Thanh
[Applause] [
Music]
[Applause] Let's
give a round of
applause to the four outstanding employees
in the
company's PR show's annual
Star Anniversary program. You
can see these are
very familiar faces,
people who have been very dedicated to their work
for many years, and
now they have been selected
through the company's voting program.
Next, we would like to invite the three winners of the
Outstanding Employee award in the
Star Anniversary program and the
Encouragement Award in the
Star Club 2007 program. We would like to welcome Mr. Ha
Quoc Ni from the IT department,
Ms. Truc Khe from the OPN department, and Ms. Pham Thi To Nga from the IA department. Please come to
the stage to receive flowers, certificates, and
gifts from the program.
Congratulations to the three
most outstanding employees of the
Star Anniversary program! You are officially joining the
Star Club 2007.
You will participate in a trip to Singapore
next year.  2008, we
would like to invite the first prize winner, Ms. Doan Thi Hong
Van,
IT department; the second prize winner, Mr. Lam Thanh Nhan,
OPI Collection Service department; and the third prize winner, Ms.
Nguyen Thi Thanh Huong, CSAA department. Please
welcome these three individuals
to the
stage once more. We would like to invite all of you,
our colleagues and the board of directors,
to give a big round of applause
to all 10 outstanding
employees of BRO company who
have excelled in the program and won the "
Outstanding Employee of BRO Company" award.
[Music]
Vietnam Will Always hold a very special
place. In My Heart and the dedication, the
energy and the effort put in by Fong in
Building the business, the support of
you guys, both staff and agency, the
support of the potential group behind
them makes it the best and most winning
combination. We
invite Ms. Truc Que, CS department; Ms. Ton
Nga, Gia Anh Duong; Mr.
Nguyen Anh Phong, OPI; Ms. Viet AV; Ms. Le
Thi Luong; Mr. Nguyen B Bach Pa; and Mr. Nguyen Chi
Dung. And we
would like to introduce to you all three of our
readers:
Ms. Nguyen Thi Thanh Vuong  Team A
won first prize for outstanding employee of
2007 with two winners in category D and two winners in category D.
Those two are Ms. Hoang Hong Van from the IT department
and Mr. Lam Thanh Nhan from the department.
We respectfully invite Mr. Long,
Mr. Nguyen, Mr. V, and Mr. Tan to step up to compete.
We will save and give thanks to the
outstanding employees of C in
2007.
Add agency leaders and Excellent Agents
for your outstanding contributions. I
think if we look back, especially proud
[music]
of leading more financially secure lives
secondly. We have been warmly embraced by
the public. It's just eight years since
we launched presential Vietnam assurance.
We now have millions of customers who
trust us with their financial planning
needs, and these are attributed to the
dedication to the professionalism and
the sheer hard work of you, our staff and
our agents. You are all the main factors
that have made Prudential Vietnam the
number one life insurer.
And you also, I know, will help Vietnam become the
leading
insurance, leading investment, and leading
finance company. [
music]
The record will be launched again in 2008.
And I encourage you all.  all of you to parp in
the Awards to make them a success to
highlight Stories Of Your colleagues Who
are living The respect prin Who are doing
their Jobs and but Doing It in the right
manner based on the right principles If
We
[music]
Hold I
know us to
forever Where the cloud
[music]
rolls for you
and
i Souls In The
Wind learn How to
bend Seek out st hold on to the
end
th
mountain There is a
fountain washes our Tears all
a
singing someone is
praying Please let us Come Home to stay
[music]
We Hold
On I know a dream will never
die Dream see us through to
forever Where clouds
roll
by for you and
when we are
out in
the
willam the
s the dark will Feel The
Light w Our
Heart
everyone I